# Mejbri Mohamed Amine

## SECOND YEAR COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING STUDENT

+216 50 77 19 60 mejbria9@gmail.com

https://github.com/mejamine

in

https://linkedin.com/in/mejbrimohamedamine

Secure an internship that provides hands-on experience in software development and enhances my technical skills. Work with a team of experienced professionals and contribute to projects that address real-world challenges while gaining knowledge and networking opportunities.

#### **EDUCATION**

# • Computer science engineering student:

Polytechnique Sousse (2022- present)

• Preparatory cycle MP:

IPEIM Mounastir (2017–2020)

• Mathematics Bachelor:

Ibn Rachik high school Kairovan (2016-2017)

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Gpro Consulting (Internship):

Developping a visit management desktop app with a search options in bothe admin and visitors interfaces.

this project includes multiple CRUDs for all entities and a searching algorithm for each entity.

(SpringBoot, PostgreSQL, Angular, REST API)

### COMMUNICATION

ARABIC, FRENSH, ENGLISH

## **CLUBS AND SOCIAL ACTIVITIES**

## cultural social project (SMILEY):

Repair of a school for Mangelian children and planning a day of different activities for these children.

2022 -- 2023

## • Orbeats Radio ENET'com:

Marketing and graphic design departement. 2021 -- 2022

#### • Enactus ENET'com:

Marketing and graphic design departement Event management departement. 2020 -- 2021

# INTERESTS

- Web development
- Devops
- Mobile development
- Al
- Sports
- Music

#### **SKILLS**

## • Programming Languages:

PHP, Python, JAVA, Java Script.

• Development tools :

Intellij IDEA, VS code, Eclipse, Pycharm , Postman, Xamp.

• Frameworks and tools :

Springboot, Symfony, pygame, angular, Node.js, React, Flutter, Grpc, REST API, GrapgQL.

data bases :

MySQL, phpMyAdmin, MongoDB, PostgreSQL.

• Graphic design:

Adobe Photoshop , Adobe Premier pro , Canva.

## UNIVERSITY EXPERIENCE

## • Ticket Management Website:

Programming a tickets management website for companies with a manager and a client interface to interact between each other. (Node.js, React, MongoDB)

Product Management Website:

Programming a productsmanagement website for companies with a client interface and an admin to controle the data. (Node.js, React, MongoDB)

• Stickers Shop Website:

Programming a stickers shop website with an admin access to manage products and orders. (Symfony, PhpMyAdmin)

Product and company management backend app:

Programming a product and company management backend app

(Node.js, phpMyAdmin, GraphQL, Grpc, REST API)

sample CRUD (blogs management):

(Node.js, React, MongoDB)

• Cars Gallery website:

Programming a car gallery website with normal access to see brands and cars, and an admin access to manage all the data in this website. (Symfony, PhpMyAdmin)

# • Rock, Paper, Scissors Mobile Application

Developping a mobile game . (Kotlin)

Basketball Legends (mini version):

Programming a basketball game inspired from basketball legends with python using pygame. (python, pygame)

• E Commerce Website :

(HTML CSS PHP)